So, we need to test Tory Trades strategy
because
some people said that, you know, maybe
trend lines do work on the longer time
frames because supposedly Tory Trades is
more of a swing trader, okay? And we're
going to test does her trading strategy
work? Does it actually generate profit?
And then on top of that, does it
generate more profit than
buying and holding the Nasdaq. Those are
the two things we need to test. So,
let's look up Tory Trades strategy.
This is funny, okay. What is What is the
The fact that people are still hyping up
trend lines is honestly insane. I've
been trading for 15 years. This should
beat me. I'm at 13. So, these guys don't
even tell you what the strategy is. So,
let's learn her strategy first of all.
Okay, this is going to
All right, there's so much here, dude.
Let me We got the idea of the trade. She
draws the trend line. She waits for the
bounce. She trails it. It's a trailing
running trade, okay? And if it closes
below her trailing stop, which is a
trend lines as well, we're going to just
go only in the trend. We're not doing
that counter trend stuff. My expectation
is this will make money. Why? Because
she's trend trading. And it's pretty
hard to lose money when you're buying an
appreciating asset. But I don't think
it's going to make more money than just
buying the in the stock market overall.
We're going to actually make it even
easier for her to win. Let's say this is
our two trend lines, okay? We've got a
bullish one. We're not going to take
shorts at all. We're not going to do
this retest thing that she does. We're
going to do the retest when it goes back
into the bullish side though, okay?
Because that way we might be able to
save our asses from all this movement
that gets lost, okay? And then we draw
safety line so we get into it like that,
okay? And then we would get out up here.
I am fully expecting that I could be
proven wrong here because this might not
be as bad as I thought, okay? I think
it's going to make money, honestly, now
that I look at it, but not for the
trading side because she's investing.
She's an investor, not a trader. Let's
do it. Let's go to the 4-hour and let's
just backtest. I'm going to do a few
data points all the way to the end of
where I can go. Let's check it out. We
entered our first trade and we're going
to let it run. So, we lost the very
first trade. Negative one R. Sweet.
Okay, cool. Next.
Oh, no. Unfortunately, we missed out.
Okay. We've got this new trend. Let's
see if we can bounce off of it, okay?
Nice. Okay, we got a bounce.
It looks like we made a little bit of
profit, okay?
If this went, you would have like if it
just ripped up, you would have had
pretty good profit and it would have
made profit. But, the reality so far is
you're not making any money. We just
took 10 potential trades. 20% were
misses, right? 80% long. We're only
doing longs, right? Cuz we're we're
we're not idiots, okay? We're not going
to short the stock market, okay? You got
a 50% win rate, okay? So, you made 1.35
R. So, she made 1
.35%
Let's see. Let's see cuz there was that
massive crash. So, guess what? 1%.
Right? It's basically a rounding error.
They're so similar. The idea that this
makes money so far based off of of 10
data points is it's on par with doing
[music] nothing. It's the same as
randomly pushing buttons, right? So far,
okay? I don't think that trend lines
make any sense to make more money than
the stock market does, okay? And that's
[music] the point of trading. Working a
job and investing is much more
profitable than what Tory Trades is
doing right now from all the data we
see. Now, how does Tory Trades make her
money? Let's look at She makes two
videos a month, okay? Looks like that.
Two videos a month and each one averages
around, let's say, 80K views, okay? Two
videos a month, so she's making 160k
views a month on YouTube, right? And I
know how much YouTube pays. It's $20 per
thousand views. I I I am a
I am a finance guy, too. So, divide that
by a thousand. So, first of all, she
makes $3,000 per month from ads on her
on her YouTube videos, okay? [music] So,
ads, $3,200, okay? And here's here's the
thing. On average, cuz again, I used to
do this, maybe 1% of your viewers will
buy your product. So, we're going to
we're going to round it down even, okay?
We're going to say 0.5% of her viewers
per month, cuz it's a it's a high ticket
price, okay? [music] We're going to say
0.5% of her viewers per month, right?
So, 160k
* 0.005.
So, 800 people per month buy her course.
It's [__] insane.
I don't know, maybe like 120 people a
month. Let's just say like a super small
amount of people buy this, right? Um
times a thousand, okay? $120,000 a
month, okay? Where does she get her
money? It's so incredibly obvious. 150k
a month off that. And then on top of
that, you know, there might be affiliate
sort of things, mentorships, brand
deals, and then also, investment. So, on
top of that, she's making another let me
be like 3% a month off of off of the
stock market. They're two What is it? 2%
a month off the stock market, right?
Let's say you get a million 1 million
dollars injected per year into the stock
market, okay? And then you make 2% per
month. So, let's say uh Nasdaq makes
18%. So, 18% of 1 million is 180k a year
off of trading. So, her claim is true
that she's making six figures a year off
of trading. It's all true because she
sells the course. She's not technically
lying. She's making an insane amount of
money from trading. 90% of the money
comes from the course, and it would not
have been possible without the capital
injection from the courses, right? And I
suspect this number is actually way
higher. If you look at TGR, he's making
millions off of his courses per month,
millions. So, I suspect Tory Trades is
probably making 500k a month off her
course. So, to to rehash this, I'm
showing you that hey, I used to do this,
too. I know how much you make. You're
deceiving people, right? You're
deceiving people because you don't make
more money. You don't get rich from the
trading. You get rich from the course,
and then money that you already have
allows you to stockpile more money from
the from the trades, which don't
actually generate alpha, but it's the
thing you do as a hobby.
Yeah, we're going to wrap it up there,
boys.
That was fun. Love y'all. Ciao, ciao.
Try waving. Try waving.